Guide to the North Carolina State University, Athletics, Football Audiovisual Materials
North Carolina State University, Athletics, Football Audiovisual Materials
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (2 of 2) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 18 Oct. 1980 (Carton 40)
- NC State vs. Virginia (1 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 20 Sept. 1980 (Carton 40)
- NC State vs. Virginia (2 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 20 Sept. 1980 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. Virginia (3 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 20 Sept. 1980 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. Virginia (4 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (black & white copy), 20 Sept. 1980 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. Virginia (5 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 20 Sept. 1980 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. Virginia (6 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (black & white copy), 20 Sept. 1980 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 27 Sept. 1980 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 27 Sept. 1980 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 27 Sept. 1980 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (4 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (black & white copy), 27 Sept. 1980 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (5 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 27 Sept. 1980 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (6 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (black & white copy), 27 Sept. 1980 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. William & Mary (1 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 6 Sept. 1980 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. William & Mary (2 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 6 Sept. 1980 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. William & Mary (3 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 6 Sept. 1980 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. William & Mary (4 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (black & white copy), 6 Sept. 1980 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. William & Mary (5 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 6 Sept. 1980 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. William & Mary (6 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (black & white copy), 6 Sept. 1980 (Carton 41)
- College Football 1980: A New Decade (NCAA Productions) (Reel 5)
- NC State vs. Clemson (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 24 Oct. 1981 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 24 Oct. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. Clemson (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 24 Oct. 1981 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. Clemson (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 24 Oct. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. Clemson (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 24 Oct. 1981 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. Clemson (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 24 Oct. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. Clemson (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 24 Oct. 1981 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. Clemson (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 24 Oct. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 14 Nov. 1981 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 14 Nov. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 14 Nov. 1981 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. Duke (4 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 14 Nov. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. Duke (5 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 14 Nov. 1981 (Carton 41)
- NC State vs. Duke (6 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 14 Nov. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. Duke (7 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 14 Nov. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. Duke (8 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 14 Nov. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. Duke (9 of 9) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 14 Nov. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (1 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 19 Sept. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (2 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 19 Sept. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (3 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 19 Sept. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (4 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 19 Sept. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (5 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 19 Sept. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (6 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 19 Sept. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (7 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 19 Sept. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (8 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 19 Sept. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (9 of 9) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 19 Sept. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 26 Sept. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 26 Sept. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 26 Sept. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 26 Sept. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. Maryland (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 26 Sept. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. Maryland (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 26 Sept. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. Maryland (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 26 Sept. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. Maryland (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 26 Sept. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. Miami (1 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 21 Nov. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. Miami (2 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 21 Nov. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. Miami (3 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 21 Nov. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. Miami (4 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 21 Nov. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. Miami (5 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 21 Nov. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. Miami (6 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 21 Nov. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. Miami (7 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 21 Nov. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. Miami (8 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 21 Nov. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. Miami (9 of 9) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 21 Nov. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. Penn State (1 of 3) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 7 Nov. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. Penn State (2 of 3) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 7 Nov. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. Penn State (3 of 3) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 7 Nov. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. Richmond (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 5 Sept. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. Richmond (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 5 Sept. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. Richmond (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 5 Sept. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. Richmond (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 5 Sept. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. Richmond (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 5 Sept. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. Richmond (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 5 Sept. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. Richmond (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 5 Sept. 1981 (Carton 42)
- NC State vs. Richmond (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 5 Sept. 1981 (Carton 95)
- NC State vs. Richmond (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking (1 of 2)], 5 Sept. 1981 (Carton 43)
- NC State vs. Richmond (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking (2 of 2)], 5 Sept. 1981 (Carton 43)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 3 minutes, 30 seconds; color; no sound
- NC State vs. South Carolina (1 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 31 Oct. 1981 (Carton 43)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (2 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 31 Oct. 1981 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (3 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 31 Oct. 1981 (Carton 43)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (4 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 31 Oct. 1981 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (5 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 31 Oct. 1981 (Carton 43)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (6 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 31 Oct. 1981 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (7 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 31 Oct. 1981 (Carton 43)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (8 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 31 Oct. 1981 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (9 of 9) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 31 Oct. 1981 (Carton 43)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (1 of 11) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 17 Oct. 1981 (Carton 43)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (2 of 11) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 17 Oct. 1981 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (3 of 11) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 17 Oct. 1981 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (4 of 11) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 17 Oct. 1981 (Carton 43)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (5 of 11) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 17 Oct. 1981 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (6 of 11) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 17 Oct. 1981 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (7 of 11) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 17 Oct. 1981 (Carton 43)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (8 of 11) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 17 Oct. 1981 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (9 of 11) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 17 Oct. 1981 (Carton 43)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (10 of 11) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 17 Oct. 1981 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (11 of 11) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 17 Oct. 1981 (Carton 43)
- NC State vs. Virgina (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 3 Oct. 1981 (Carton 43)
- NC State vs. Virgina (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 3 Oct. 1981 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. Virgina (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 3 Oct. 1981 (Carton 43)
- NC State vs. Virgina (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 3 Oct. 1981 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. Virgina (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 3 Oct. 1981 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. Virgina (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 3 Oct. 1981 (Carton 43)
- NC State vs. Virgina (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 3 Oct. 1981 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. Virgina (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 3 Oct. 1981 (Carton 43)
- NC State vs. Virgina (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 3 Oct. 1981 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. Richmond (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 3 Oct. 1981 (Carton 43)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 12 Sept. 1981 (Carton 43)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 12 Sept. 1981 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 12 Sept. 1981 (Carton 43)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (4 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 12 Sept. 1981 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (5 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 12 Sept. 1981 (Carton 43)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (6 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 12 Sept. 1981 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (7 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 12 Sept. 1981 (Carton 43)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (8 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 12 Sept. 1981 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (9 of 9) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 12 Sept. 1981 (Carton 43)
- Wolfpack Attack! (football highlights), 1981 (Carton 43)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 14 minutes, 15 seconds; color; sound
- College Football 1981: A Balance of Power (NCAA Productions) (Reel 4)
- NC State vs. Clemson (1 of 2) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 23 Oct. 1982 (Carton 43)
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 2) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 23 Oct. 1982 (Carton 43)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 2) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 13 Nov. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 2) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 13 Nov. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 11 Sept. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 11 Sept. 1982 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 11 Sept. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 11 Sept. 1982 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 11 Sept. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 11 Sept. 1982 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 11 Sept. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 11 Sept. 1982 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. Furman (1 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 4 Sept. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. Furman (2 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 4 Sept. 1982 (Carton 96)
- NC State vs. Furman (3 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 4 Sept. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. Furman (4 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 4 Sept. 1982 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. Furman (5 of 6) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 4 Sept. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. Furman (6 of 6) [labeled on canister asDefense, Kicking], 4 Sept. 1982 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 25 Sept. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 25 Sept. 1982 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 25 Sept. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 25 Sept. 1982 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. Maryland (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 25 Sept. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. Maryland (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 25 Sept. 1982 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. Maryland (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 25 Sept. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. Maryland (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 25 Sept. 1982 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. Maryland (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 25 Sept. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. Maryland (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking, Defense], 25 Sept. 1982 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. Miami (Florida) (1 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 20 Nov. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. Miami (Florida) (2 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 20 Nov. 1982 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. Miami (Florida) (3 of 4) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 20 Nov. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. Miami (Florida) (4 of 4) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 20 Nov. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. Penn State (1 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 6 Nov. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. Penn State (2 of 4) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 6 Nov. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. Penn State (3 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 6 Nov. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. Penn State (4 of 4) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 6 Nov. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (1 of 2) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 30 Oct. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (2 of 2) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 30 Oct. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (1 of 3) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 16 Oct. 1982 (Carton 44)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (2 of 3) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 16 Oct. 1982 (Carton 45)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (3 of 3) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 16 Oct. 1982 (Carton 45)
- NC State vs. Virginia (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 2 Oct. 1982 (Carton 45)
- NC State vs. Virginia (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 2 Oct. 1982 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. Virginia (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 2 Oct. 1982 (Carton 45)
- NC State vs. Virginia (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 2 Oct. 1982 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. Virginia (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 2 Oct. 1982 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. Virginia (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 2 Oct. 1982 (Carton 45)
- NC State vs. Virginia (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 2 Oct. 1982 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. Virginia (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 2 Oct. 1982 (Carton 45)
- NC State vs. Virginia (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 2 Oct. 1982 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. Virginia (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 2 Oct. 1982 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 18 Sept. 1982 (Carton 45)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 18 Sept. 1982 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 18 Sept. 1982 (Carton 45)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (4 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 18 Sept. 1982 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (5 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 18 Sept. 1982 (Carton 45)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (6 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 18 Sept. 1982 (Carton 45)
- College Football '82: Contenders All (NCAA Productions), 1982 (Reel 12)
- NC State vs. Appalachian State University (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 5 Nov. 1983 (Carton 45)
  This film has been converted to digital beta (also stored in carton 45), and is also stored as an mp4 file from which copies can be reproduced.
- NC State vs. Appalachian State University (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 5 Nov. 1983 (Carton 45)
- NC State vs. Appalachian State University (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 5 Nov. 1983 (Carton 45)
- NC State vs. Appalachian State University (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 5 Nov. 1983 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. Appalachian State University (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 5 Nov. 1983 (Carton 45)
- NC State vs. Appalachian State University (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 5 Nov. 1983 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. Appalachian State University (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 5 Nov. 1983 (Carton 45)
- NC State vs. Appalachian State University (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 5 Nov. 1983 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. The Citadel (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 17 Sept. 1983 (Carton 45)
- NC State vs. The Citadel (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 17 Sept. 1983 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. The Citadel (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 17 Sept. 1983 (Carton 45)
- NC State vs. The Citadel (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 17 Sept. 1983 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. The Citadel (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 17 Sept. 1983 (Carton 45)
- NC State vs. The Citadel (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 17 Sept. 1983 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. The Citadel (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 17 Sept. 1983 (Carton 45)
- NC State vs. The Citadel (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 17 Sept. 1983 (Carton 97)
- NC State vs. The Citadel (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 17 Sept. 1983 (Carton 45)
- NC State vs. The Citadel (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 17 Sept. 1983 (Carton 98)
- NC State vs. Clemson (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 22 Oct. 1983 (Carton 45)
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 22 Oct. 1983 (Carton 98)
- NC State vs. Clemson (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 22 Oct. 1983 (Carton 45)
- NC State vs. Clemson (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 22 Oct. 1983 (Carton 98)
- NC State vs. Clemson (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 22 Oct. 1983 (Carton 45)
- NC State vs. Clemson (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 22 Oct. 1983 (Carton 98)
- NC State vs. Clemson (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 22 Oct. 1983 (Carton 46)
- NC State vs. Clemson (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 22 Oct. 1983 (Carton 98)
- NC State vs. Clemson (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 22 Oct. 1983 (Carton 46)
- NC State vs. Clemson (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 22 Oct. 1983 (Carton 98)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 10 Nov. 1983 (Carton 46)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 10 Nov. 1983 (Carton 98)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 10 Nov. 1983 (Carton 46)
- NC State vs. Duke (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 10 Nov. 1983 (Carton 98)
- NC State vs. Duke (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 10 Nov. 1983 (Carton 46)
- NC State vs. Duke (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 10 Nov. 1983 (Carton 98)
- NC State vs. Duke (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 10 Nov. 1983 (Carton 46)
- NC State vs. Duke (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 10 Nov. 1983 (Carton 98)
- NC State vs. Duke (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 10 Nov. 1983 (Carton 46)
- NC State vs. Duke (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 10 Nov. 1983 (Carton 98)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 10 Sept. 1983 (Carton 46)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 10 Sept. 1983 (Carton 98)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 10 Sept. 1983 (Carton 46)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 10 Sept. 1983 (Carton 98)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 10 Sept. 1983 (Carton 46)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 10 Sept. 1983 (Carton 98)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 10 Sept. 1983 (Carton 46)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 10 Sept. 1983 (Carton 98)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 10 Sept. 1983 (Carton 46)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 10 Sept. 1983 (Carton 98)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (1 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 8 Oct. 1983 (Carton 46)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (2 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 8 Oct. 1983 (Carton 98)